<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
  <categories>
  </categories>
  <apps>
  <app id="ood-ood-ealthy-recipes-cookbook"><name>BBC Good Food – Healthy recipes cookbook</name><version>1.2.0.3</version><icon>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/healthy.logo.270x270-1779416589.png</icon><publisher>BBC Worldwide Ltd</publisher><featured>false</featured><description>Healthy food needn't be boring! This app has over 195 recipes for you to incorporate into your day-to-day cooking. More than 195 recipes to help tempt you to cook and eat healthily year-round, including Salmon &amp; ginger fish cakes, Thai beef stir-fry and Indian butternut squash curry. Once you've downloaded the app, you can use and search the recipes at any time, even offline. There's something for everyone, and every meal (including breakfast). The app contains over 35 recipes that have less than 200 calories per portion, as well as healthy twists on classic dishes, like Chicken korma and Chocolate brownies - so you’re sure to keep your friends and family happy too. Each recipe has full nutritional information, such as protein, fat carbs, sugar and kcals. You can switch between metric and imperial measurements. The app also has five helpful videos and details on eight healthy ingredients to add into your diet. --------------------------------------- Want more? Visit us at bbcgoodfood.com, for over 7,000 recipes all triple-tested by the in-house cookery team. --------------------------------------- This app is produced by BBC Worldwide, the commercial arm of the BBC. BBC Worldwide is self-funded and returns profits to the BBC to be reinvested in programmes and services to help keep the UK licence fee as low as possible. For those who wonder why our apps aren't free, BBC Worldwide has the responsibility of channelling funds back to the BBC, so the BBC can continue to create amazing content.</description><package>https://appxboxdl.dankassassin368.com/Windows%208.1%20APPX%20Files/Apps/BBC%20Cookbook/BBCWorldwideLtd.BBCGoodFoodHealthyrecipescookbook_2025.0.0.0_neutral_~_g2s5c4trewyqj.appxbundle</package><screenshot1>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/bbcgoodfood1-1779416590.png</screenshot1><screenshot2>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/bbcgoodfood2-1779416592.png</screenshot2><screenshot3>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/bbcgoodfood3-1779416593.png</screenshot3><screenshot4>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/bbcgoodfood4-1779416596.png</screenshot4><screenshot5>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/bbcgoodfood5-1779416598.png</screenshot5><pcCapable>true</pcCapable><mobileCapable>false</mobileCapable><win81compatible>true</win81compatible></app></apps>
</data>
